C'mon, what's the problem?
The usual.
Well, that was fast.
I figured you'd probably
be coming in sometime soon.
Doesn't seem like you've been
waiting for me since yesterday.
Obviously not.
Fredi, could you come here?
Hey, hang on!
Cindy!
Sheesh, if you keep bothering
me, I'll never get any work done!
What's your problem with me?
Me, I don't like guys who chase me.
Actually, I'm the type
who likes to do the chasing!
What are you talking about?
So what kind of guy are
you looking for, then?
A real man! I like 'em
wild, sexy, and intelligent!
But still kind to women, and always relaxed.
And he's gotta be cute.
Like Dante!
Dante?
Him.
If you could become more like Dante,
I might think about going out with you!
Hey, Cindy!
She thinks that's a real man?
I don't get it...
What does Cindy see in that guy?
What the...?
Did I drink too much?
She's not here! She's not here!
Where'd that woman go?!
Oh, my. What's his deal?
No. Wait! This isn't...
Forget about that guy!
What happened to your face?!
Ow!
Cindy, listen and listen good.
That Dante guy is no "real man."
He's nothing but a pervert!
What?
I saw it with my own eyes!
He went into the girls' restroom!
What are you talking about?
What I'm saying is that he
picked up some girl at this club,
took her to the women's restroom and...
Dammit!
Dammit... I swear I'm
going to get the dirt on you.
Hey, what d'ya think you're doing?!
Uh, n-n-nothing...
Looks like business is slow as always, eh?
Whatever... Let's see it.
Now, take it easy. Look, here we go.
Be careful.
Like you give a shit...
What the hell are you doing here, Dante?
I came to give you a message...
"You guys don't need a thing like this."
No way! He's going to take on the Mafia?!
H-He really did...
Wh-Who is this guy?!
Is he out of his mind?!
Stay away from that guy!
He's heartless and cold-blooded!
It doesn't matter if it's the Mafia or whoever!
That dude will even kill people for money!
It wouldn't matter if you had nine lives!
If you're with that guy, you'll just
get used and then riddled with holes!
"Riddled with holes"? That's awful!
No, wait! You're misunderstanding me!
Go home.
Ah, don't be that way...
What the heck? The door isn't even locked...
This is what I should
have done in the first place.
I don't care what it is...
I just need to find something that
will land this freak in the slammer.
I could make your wish come true.
Must be my imagination...
Naw... I'm the only one fit for that job.
You despise Dante, right?! Me too!
You gotta let me out of here!
You?! What the hell could you do?!
I'll make this worth your while, little boy.
Let me out of here, and I'll...
Don't listen to those morons!
Me, I'm the one you need!
--I'm the one who found this guy!
--Ouch!
--So get lost!
Hey! Let me out of here!
What the hell were those things?!
They're devils.
Wh-Who are you?!
I don't think you've got the right to ask
that, after breaking into someone's house.
I... That's...
Relax. I won't tell Dante.
So, you want to know the
truth about Dante, don't you?
Huh?
If so, I've got something nice for you.
What is this?
Don't ask. Just take it and go.
When you open it, you'll
know what Dante really is.
Dante?
You're home, aren't you?
Morrison told me...
--Huh?
--It sounds like you've made a bunch of money, haven't you?
Hey, it's true, Cindy!
You gotta believe me! I
saw it with my own eyes!
That dude isn't normal!
There's something really weird about him!
You broke into Dante's
place when he wasn't there?
That? Um... Well...
It's 'cause I wanted you to
know that he's dangerous...
Shame on you!
Why did things turn out like this?
Owww...
Huh?
Huh? Dammit!
Trying to make me look stupid...
My family have been pacifists
since my grandfather's time, but...
What, just a cat?
It's all right. Come on...
I'm not going to eat you or anything...
Wh-Who's that over there?
What the hell is that?!
There he is!
Run, you idiot!
What nice timing...
Lately I've had nothing
to fight but weaklings.
So I've been wanting to go up against
someone that can give me a bit of a workout!
A dem... A demo...
All bark and no bite.
It's true! You gotta believe me, Cindy!
I saw that dude hack a devil in two!
And there's more! Listen!
He's a devil! It's absolutely true!
That guy's a devil himself!
I can't believe you... Are you all right?
The sun's high in the sky, but
it's like you're still half dreaming.
Nonsense! I didn't dream up any of this!
At any rate, that guy is...
Welcome, Dante!
Hey, settle down!
Who's that? Your boyfriend?
I was actually thinking
about maybe dating him...
But he's been getting all weird lately.
Maybe I just didn't put things right.
All I meant was that I'd
like him to be more like you...
It looks like he misunderstood me.
And now he says I should stay
away from you 'cause you're a devil!
Well, he's got things about half right...
And he swears he saw
you kill a devil last night...
It's so stupid. It's just that I
wanted to be the one to chase him...
Oh, I'm sorry! You'll have the usual, right?
Yep, that's right.
You sure can be a devil...
Who's the devil?!
If you're going to lose
the money to me at pool,
wouldn't you be better off
just paying what you owe?
Are you really that far in debt?
I mean, some weird man's been
spying on your office lately, too.
A weird man?
Yeah. But he seemed like a
total wimp, so I got rid of him!
That reminds me...
there was some visitor in your office
when I stopped by recently, too.
A visitor?
Dammit!
Oh crap!
Dante!
U-Um... behind you...
You called?
--You ready?
--Huh?
Now the party really gets started.
N-No! Stop!
All right, bring it on!
Just a minute.
You forgot something.
If you're going to skip town,
you should at least let her know.
If you don't she can't chase
you, even if she wants to.
What do you mean by that?
Ask her yourself.
Wait, you came all this way to tell me that?
I'm a devil.
I just hadn't had my fill of fun yet.
Dante!
What are you?!
Who knows... Maybe you
should try asking God or someone.
I'll have the same!
Huh?
I said I want one of those, too!
All right!
Fredi, one strawberry sundae!
You planning on eating with me?
Yeah.
There you go.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here's your strawberry sundae!
This guy's a total dork.
I'm not sure when it started,
but before I knew it, I was
always listening to her songs.
More rudely than any man,
more delicately than any woman,
she sang of the sadness in human hearts.
If I ever get to meet her,
I'll probably thank her.
Because she made me realize that
even I have enough emotional depth
to understand songs.